Lighting is chosen from drawings and catalogs,
but homeowners cannot easily imagine the atmosphere it will create.
How bright will the room feel? How will warm and neutral light change it?
Fixing a poor choice after construction costs real money.
Lighting Lab lets homeowners try lighting plans in their own floor plan,
with no CAD skills required.
Import your own floor plan, then select a light.
Change its color temperature from 2700K to 3500K.
Lower or raise brightness, compare another position,
and adjust how widely the light spreads.
Try several options in 2D, then switch to 3D
to see the walls, furniture, and room as a whole.
The finished look includes indirect light.
Compare options until they fit how you want to use the room.
2D and 3D stay in sync, and projects save and reopen
in the browser—on a PC or a phone.
Codex with GPT-5.6 reviewed believable lighting and everyday-device performance,
then supported mobile improvements, English, tests, and the public release.
Compare color temperature, brightness, position, and distribution
in your own floor plan—before construction.